const quizData = [
    {
      question: "How much exercise should you get in a day?",
      a: "30 min",
      b: "1 hour",
      c: "None",
      d: "1+ hours",
      correct: "a", // https://www.mayoclinic.org/healthy-lifestyle/fitness/expert-answers/exercise/faq-20057916
    }, 
    {
      question: "What percentage of your meal should be fruits and vegetables?",
      a: "25$",
      b: "None",
      c: "100%",
      d: "50%",
      correct: "d",  // https://med.libretexts.org/Courses/Sierra_College/Sierra%3A_NUTF10_(Teh)/02%3A_Achieving_a_Healthy_Diet/2.06%3A_My_Plate_-_A_Guide_for_Eating_More_Healthfully
    }, 
      {
      question: "What percentage of your meal should be grains and protein?",
      a: "50%",
      b: "25%",
      c: "75%",
      d: "15%",
      correct: "a", // https://med.libretexts.org/Courses/Sierra_College/Sierra%3A_NUTF10_(Teh)/02%3A_Achieving_a_Healthy_Diet/2.06%3A_My_Plate_-_A_Guide_for_Eating_More_Healthfully
    }, 
      {
      question: "How much water should you be drinking a day?",
      a: "1 Gallon (Men) 0.8 Gallon (Women)",
      b: "18.5 Cups (Men) and 14.5 Cups (Women)",
      c: "15.5 Cups (Men) and 11.5 Cups (Women)",
      d: "24.0 Cups (Men) and 20.0 Cups (Women)",
      correct: c, // https://www.mayoclinic.org/healthy-lifestyle/nutrition-and-healthy-eating/in-depth/water/art-20044256 
    }, 
      {
      question: "Should your diet consist of green vegetables?",
      a: "Yes",
      b: "I am not sure",
      c: "No",
      d: "Depends on what your doctor says.",
      correct: "a", 
    }, 
      {
      question: "What does a healthy diet look to you?",
      a: "Apples, Bananas, Chicken, Dark Chocolate, Rice, Brocolli",
      b: "Milk, Whole Grain Cereal, Oranges, Beef, Hamburger, Lettuce",
      c: "Pasta, Garlic Bread, Pizza, House Salad with Dressing, Smoothie",
      d: "ALL OF THE ABOVE",
      correct: "d", 
    }, 
      {
      question: "",
      a: "",
      b: "",
      c: "",
      d: "",
      correct: , 
    }, 
      {
      question: "",
      a: "",
      b: "",
      c: "",
      d: "",
      correct: , 
    }, 
      {
      question: "",
      a: "",
      b: "",
      c: "",
      d: "",
      correct: , 
    }, 
      {
      question: "",
      a: "",
      b: "",
      c: "",
      d: "",
      correct: , 
    }, 
  ]